WANAWANA
Gutto Good hajiketeru
グッと Good 弾ける
Angai nandai hamatten jan
案外なんだい ハマってんじゃん
Hito mishiri shiteru hima ni hajimeyou!
人見知りしてる暇に 始めよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
"Haganai"
クールに見えて 実は超寂しい
Kuuru ni miete, jitsu wa chou sabishii
(Mosou nara bai, bai, bai
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
妄想ならバイバイバイ
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Nani fujiyuu naku, dakedo tarinai
何不自由なく だけど足りない
(Riajuu kara tooi, tooi, tooi?
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
リア充から遠い遠い遠い
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Zannen doushi de atsumattara
残念同士で 集まったら
Ah- yosou ga dekinai
Ah- 予想が出来ない 展開の 地雷を踏んだ
Tenkai no jirai wo funda!
SOWASOWA
絶対絶対覗きたい
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
Koukai hyakkai shitakunaitte
後悔100回したくないって
Tsumannai puraido nante
sutekicchatte furikicchatte
つまんない プライドなんて
捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Zannen kannen shite mitara,
angai nandai hamatten jan
残念観念してみたら
案外なんだいハマってんじゃん
Butsukatte, dogimagi atte, mitsukeyou!
ぶつかって どぎまぎ合って 見つけよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
絶対絶対覗きたい
You! Sutekicchatte furikicchatte
YOU！ 捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Yes! Doudai? Doudai, sokontoko
Yes！ どーだいどーだいそこんとこ
"We Don't Have Any Friends"
本字幕由诸神卖萌组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神卖萌组---
日听：apollius   翻译: Justin    校对：喵儿 小草爱吃梨
时间轴：nono   后期：Maize
"We Don't Have Many Friends"
Mikazuki.
三日月
Here!
はい
Hurry up and take your seat.
早く席に着きなさい
はい
Yes, Sir.
...Sora?
空
Long time no see, Taka.
久しぶり 鷹
This has been... our first meeting in ten years.
それは鷹との十年ぶりの出会いだった
フランス そして神聖ローマ帝国が応じて第3
As for France and the Holy
Roman Empire, the Third Crusade...
アイツが転校してきたのは
When he transferred here... that's right...
そう 確か衣替えの頃だった
It was right around our seasonal uniform change.
Um... I'm... the transfer student...
あの 俺 転校生の
は  はい
Uh... okay!
Hasegawa... Kodaka!
羽瀬川小鷹
- Osada-sensei...
- What? Did he attack her?
麻田先生 を襲った
不良  転校生
- Is he a delinquent?!
- What? Did he attack her?
The new student?!
Look at that hair!
見ろよ あの髪
Taka...
鷹
It's Taka! The color of that hair,
the expression of those eyes...
鷹だ あの髪の色 あの目付き
It's definitely him!
間違いない
He hasn't changed at all in the last ten years.
アイツは十年前から何も変わっていない
He always did suck at smiling,
いつも笑顔を作るのがへたくそで
and the more effort he used
to put into trying to be friendly,
人に対して友好的に接しようと努力するほど裏目に出るのだ
the more it backfired on him.
He's...
アイツは
あ 教科書
Textbook...
H-Here...
こ これ
"World History II"
Thank...
ありが
Yep. He's Taka.
そう アイツは鷹だ
My one and only close friend back then...
私の ただ一人の親友だった
He didn't even notice!
気づかないし
Well, what do you think, Tomo-chan?
なあ トモちゃんはどう思う
Yeah, him.
そう アイツ
Hasegawa Kodaka, the guy
who hasn't seen me in ten years,
十年ぶりに会ったのに
一向に私の事を思い出そうとしない 羽瀬川小鷹
and who hasn't made the
slightest effort to remember me.
Isn't that terrible?
ひどくないか
Yeah... well, it's because I used
to dress like a boy ten years ago.
そりゃあ十年前の私は男みたいな格好してたからな
I understand that, but...
それはわかってるんだが
What?! I should talk to him first?!
そんな 私から声をかけるなんて
そもそも私自分から人にどうやって話しかけたらいいかわからないし
In the first place, I don't know how
to start a conversation with someone...
So I'm trying to get him to talk to me.
だから話しかけてもらう努力はしてるって
When I arrive at school...
学校に来る時も 放課後教室から出る時も
When I leave the classroom after school...
When I take things out of my locker...
ロッカーから物を取る時も 戻す時も
Or put them back in...
I always walk by him...
必ずアイツの側を通っているのに
...but he never says a word to me.
アイツは一言も声をかけてこないんだ
Don't tease me! It is not!
からかうなよ  そんな事ないって
It's my fault?
悪いのは私だって
That's what you always say!
すぐそう事言う
What should we do on the way home?
Wanna stop by somewhere?
ね 帰りどうする  どこか寄ってく
Yeah, how about that accessories
shop across from the station?
うん 駅向こうの小物屋さんとかどう
Now that you mention it, that time you...
そういえば  あの時
No, no I can't believe this!
そんなそんなそんな
He... Kodaka... saw me?!
アイツに 小鷹に見られた 今の光景を
Could he hear me talking?!
聞かれた
Don't tell me he heard what I was saying?!
まさか 話している内容まで
This is bad. This is really,
really bad! What should I do?!
まずいまずいまずい どうしよう
What?!
何だ
Um, can you...
その もしかして幽霊とか見えたりするのか
...see ghosts and stuff like that?
Huh? Ghosts don't exist!
はあ 幽霊なんているわけがないだろ
But you were talking to somebody...
でも さっきまで誰かと話し
見ていたのか
You were watching me?!
わ  私は友達と話していただけだ
I-I was just talking to my friend!
My air friend!
エア友達と
That was the first conversation
I'd had with Taka in ten years.
これが 私と鷹の十年ぶりに話した 最初の会話だった
I've got it! A club!
そうか 部活だ
See you later, Kodaka!
じゃあな 小鷹
That's it! A club!
そうだ 部活だ
ほら 創部の申請書
Here's the application to establish a new club.
Thank you!
ありがとうございます
If I'm not in a club, I can make one!
部活がなければ 作ればいいんだ
A club for just Kodaka and me!
小鷹と二人きりの部活を
Sometimes I use this chapel
when I want to read somewhere quiet
ここの礼拝堂は静かに本を読みたい時や
or when the library's crowded.
図書館が混んでいる時 偶に使う
It's a really comfortable place.
実に快適な場所だ
"Common Room 4"
It's a really comfortable place.
Sister Takayama Maria is in charge of this room.
この部屋を管理しているのがシスター高山マリア
Apparently, she's still a child...
まだ子供らしい
まあ 子供は嫌いじゃない
Well, I don't hate kids.
Excuse me...
失礼します
Wh-What the hell do you want?!
な 何なのだ 貴様は
This is my holy nap room!
ここは私の神聖なるお昼寝るルームで
貴様のようなクズが来ていい場所ではないぞ
It's not a place for scum like you!
"Extracurricular Club Prospectus"
あの 私は二年五組の三日月夜空と言います
Um...
I'm Mikazuki Yozora from class 2-5.
I have to ask you, Takayama Maria-sensei...
高山マリア先生にお願いが
いやだ
Forget it!
This little brat...
このガキ
Um, could you just hear me out first?
えっと まずは話だけでも聞いて
What do I care about that, poopy?!
そんなの知るか  うんこ
How about I pop you one?!
殴ろうか
I want to make a new club and
I was hoping to use this room...
新しく部を作りたいのですが
ここの部屋を使わせて
No way! Get the hell out of here, stupid poop!
いやだ さっさと帰れ バカうんこ
All right!
よし
Kodaka, follow me.
小鷹 ちょっと こい
Mikazuki talked to him!
三日月が話しかけた
To the new guy?!
え 転校生と
Yes. This is what a club is!
そう これは部活だ
The purpose is to make friends.
活動目的は友達を作る事
Yes, a club for me and
Kodaka... Sora and Taka...
そう 私と小鷹が 空と鷹が
再び 友達になるための部活動だ
...to become friends once again!
移ろう雲に流れ
Drifting in the clouds...
どこか　浮かぶ愛しい笑顔
A dear smile is floating somewhere.
どうして　遠ざけてしまったんだろう
I wonder why I pushed it away?
二人のとき
Time just for the two of us...
僕が弱すぎて守れなかった
I was too weak to protect you
From the rain that kept
falling, trying to break us up.
切り裂くように降り続く雨
But now I understand what was in your eyes.
今頃わかったよ
君の瞳に映るのは強さで包み込む言葉で
The strength that was reflected there,
The words you embraced me with,
They're not in my heart...
僕の胸の中にそれはいなくて
あの日君が最後につぶやくように
What you murmured to me that last time,
搾り出した一言を僕に返す
Those words that you squeezed
out run through my head.
涙声の「じゃあね」
"Take care," you said in a tearful voice.
Your cheeks flushed red.
赤くなった頬に
This hand that reached out to
touch them had never looked so filthy...
伸ばしかけたこの手は
ひどく汚れて見えて
As when I changed to a season of one...
僕は一人　季節交代だ
Hey, Hasegawa!
おい 羽瀬川
Why is he looking at Mikazuki?
何で三日月を見てるんだ
I wonder why the two of them are standing up...
二人立って どうしたのかしら
All right, continuing with attendance...
え では出席の続きだ
Miyajima.
宮島
はい
Here.
Butou.
武藤
Here!
はい
Yaegashi.
八重樫  八重樫
Yaegashi?
あ はい います
Y-Yes, I'm here!
- Good. Yamazaki.
- Here.
よし 山崎
はい
That's right...
そうなの
H-Hey...
な なあ
What?
何だ
Um, what happened to your hair?
いや その髪 どうしたんだ
Cut it.
切った
Yeah, I can see that...
そりゃ見りゃわかるけど
...but why all of a sudden?
だから 何で急に
The night of the summer festival...
夏祭りの夜
But that was just the tip, a little bit, right?
でもあれは先っぽの方をちょっとだけだったろ
You didn't have to cut it all...
そんなバッサリ切って
It's because you doused my whole head!
お前が頭から思いきりぶっかけたからだ
No matter how many times I washed my
hair, the weird stink wouldn't come out...
髪を洗ってもなかなか落ちないし
変な臭いもついてしまったし
I-I'm really sorry...
ごめんなさい ホントに
He doused her whole head?
頭からぶっかけた
He says "just the tip," but he forced her?!
先っぽだけって言いながら無理やり
Mikazuki-san resisted, so he...
抵抗する三日月さんを
洗い落とせない変な臭いの白い液体を
She washed and washed, but couldn't
get the weird stink of the white fluid out!
Th-That's not!
ち ちが  白い液体なんて
No one said anything about white fluid!
ちょ ちょっと来い
C-Come here a second!
Hey! Wait... Yozora!
おい ちょっと 夜空
I...
その ええと
Um...
What I'm trying to say...
だ～か～ら 私が空なのでした
...is that I was Sora!
What do you think?!
何か感想は
Um... I'm surprised.
ええと びっくりした
Well, what else?!
他にないのか
What else?
他に
You know, like...
だからその
You're happy... or honored... or moved?
嬉しいとか光栄ですとか 感動したとか
なんつうか 戸惑ってるっていうか
How do I put it? It's like I'm bewildered...
I guess "surprised" is the
strongest feeling, after all.
やっぱりびっくりしたってのが一番強いかな
That haircut suits you pretty well.
その髪型 けっこう似合ってるな
へ  変じゃないか
I-It's not strange?
お おう 変じゃない
No. It's not strange.
そ そうか
O-Oh...
I-I went to a hair salon.
び 美容院に行ったのだ
A... A hair salon? That's somethin'.
美容院か それはすごいな
I was nervous.
緊張した
I would think so.
緊張するよな
へえ 俺が転校してきて時から気づいてたのか
You realized it when I transferred here?!
Yeah. From the very beginning.
あ 最初からだ
I'm surprised you knew it was me.
よくわかったな
ふん そのプリン頭は見間違いようもない
I would recognize that pudding head anywhere.
I see. You've sure got a
way of convincing a guy.
なるほど すごい説得力だ
Huh? But when we first talked in the classroom,
あれ でもお前 俺と教室で初めて話した時
didn't you say something
about not remembering my name?
俺の名前も覚えてないような事言ってなかったか
ふん お前が気づいてないのに
It was irritating that I recognized you,
but you didn't recognize me.
私だけ気づいているのがしゃくだったのだ
That's why you pretended you didn't know?
だから知らんぶりをしてたのか
That's right.
そうだ
A dead-end?
行き止まりか
それは悪かったよ
Well, I apologize for that.
But how can you blame me for not realizing?
いやでも 俺が気づかなかったのはしょうがないだろう
I thought he... I mean you... were a b-boy...
俺は昔のお前の事  お 男だと思ってたんだから
I never said I was a boy back then!
私は一言も自分が男だなんて言った事はなかったぞ
You don't normally think someone's a girl
男みたいな格好して  やたら喧嘩っ早いやつなんて
when they wear boys' clothes
and are quick to pick fights.
普通は女だとは思わないっての
You're the one who disappeared
before I could confess that I was a girl!
女だって告白する前にいなくなったのはそっちじゃないか
ま まさか あの時言ってた大事な話って
You mean that "important thing"
you were going to tell me was...
Yeah.
But you never showed up that day!
でも だってお前 あの日 来なかったじゃないか
それは
That was... Well, that was...
それは だって
I was embarrassed to show you...
恥ずかしかったのだ
お前にその
...t- to show you what I looked like in a skirt.
ス スカート姿を見せるのが
スカート
Skirt?
I wore a skirt the day I was going
to confess to you that I was a girl...
私はあの日 自分が女だと告白するために
スカートを穿いてきたのだ
...but I'd never worn a skirt before,
でもスカートなんて穿いた事なくて
so I didn't know if it
looked okay on me or not...
似合ってるかどうかわからなくて
I thought maybe you'd laugh at me.
もしかしたら笑われるんじゃないかと思って
And so...
それで
...I just couldn't show myself to you.
お前の前に出る事がどうしてもできなかった
I might've mustered up the courage to do it
お前が引っ越すのを知ってれば
勇気を振り絞ることができたかもしれないのに
if I'd known you were going to move, but...
In other words, it's all your fault!
つまり全部お前が悪い
Why?!
何でだよ
In the first place, there was no
need to wear a skirt to confess...
つーか 告白するためにわざわざスカート穿くなんて
ふん お前の事だから
Knowing you, I figured you
wouldn't believe me if I just told you.
口で言うだけでは信じられないと思っただけだ
Well, you were probably right...
まあ 確かに
Oh, and also, the fact
that you and I were frie...
なあ それと 私とお前が友だ
The fact that we were childhood acquaintances is
幼い頃に知り合っていたことは隣人部の連中には秘密だぞ
a secret from the rest of the Neighbors Club.
Why?
なんで
There's no reason to tell everybody.
言いふらすことでもないだろう
Okay, I guess...
まあ いいけど
Then we'll leave it at that.
わかればいい
Now, let's go.
では行くぞ
That's right!
そうだ
What should I call you from now on?
これから お前の事 何て呼べばいいんだ
Yozora! Just Yozora.
夜空 呼び捨てで 夜空だ
Hey, don't you have some sorta nickname?!
なあ 何かあだ名とかないのか
I do. I did.
ある あった
I did, but I'm not going to
tell you what it was, Kodaka.
あったけど 小鷹には教えない
Why not?
何で
Because only friends use
nicknames with each other.
あだ名は友達同士で使うものだからな
Hi!
おーす
あ 小鷹先輩 こんにちは
Kodaka-sempai, hello...
- oooooooooooooooooooo!
A two-shot of Kodaka-sempai
and a mystery stud-muffin!
小鷹先輩と謎のイケメンのツーショットキタ
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Who is the stud-muffin, Sempai?!
どどどどちら様ですか先輩 そのイケメンの方は
Um, "stud-muffin"?
いや イケメンって
だって スカート
See the skirt?
あ いえ 答えを言うのはちょっと待ってください
No, wait before you answer!
理科が推理してみせます
Rika will try to deduce it!
つまり 小鷹先輩の後輩
Cut to the chase! Kodaka-sempai's junior!
外れ
Wrong.
Kodaka-sempai's senior?!
小鷹先輩の先輩
違う
No.
小鷹先輩の弟さん
Kodaka-sempai's younger brother?!
いないよ
I don't have one.
Kodaka-sempai's older...
小鷹先輩のお兄
兄貴でもないぞ
I don't have a big brother either!
うん 小鷹先輩のサッカー部でのライバル
Kodaka-sempai's soccer club rival!
いつからサッカー部になったんだ 俺は
When did I join the soccer club?
小鷹先輩の生徒会長
Kodaka-sempai's student body president!
意味がよくわからん
I don't really understand that one...
小鷹先輩のいいなずけ
Kodaka-sempai's fiancé?!
How did you come up with that?!
何でそうなる
Aniki has bonded with a stud-muffin...
兄貴がイケメンの方と契りを
な 何を言ってる 幸村
Wh-What are you saying, Yukimura?!
I wonder which one's dominant
and which one's submissive?
どっちが受けでどっちが攻めなんでしょうねえ
Is Sempai aggressively dominant?
先輩の強気攻め 誘い受け ヘタレ攻め ヘタレ受け
Masochistically submissive?
Reluctantly dominant?
Reluctantly submissive? Cold-bloodedly
dominant? Cold-bloodedly submissive?
鬼畜攻め 鬼畜受け
Oh, just imagining it makes Rika...
もう想像してるだけで理科は
Makes Rika...
理科はもう
Damned pervert.
この変態め
Get a grip. This is...
落ち着け コイツは
Huh?
あれ 夜空 髪切ったの
Yozora... You got a haircut?
Y-Yeah. As you can see, Meat...
あ  あ 見ての通りだ 肉
Yozora... Anego?
夜空の姉御
Huh? Yozora... sempai?
夜空先輩
That's right. It's Yozora.
そうだ 夜空だ
You chopped a lot off, huh?
けっこうバッサリ切っちゃったのね
So, why'd you do it?
ね 何で何で
It has nothing to do with you, wretch.
貴様には関係ないだろう
いいじゃない教えてくれても
Why not tell me? You don't lose anything by it!
減るもんじゃないし
私の貴重な時間は減るだろ
I'd lose my precious time!
What, are you saying that
talking to me is a waste of time?!
あたしとの会話は時間の無駄って事
ようやくわか
- You finally understand, Meat...
- Things are back to normal.
いつも通りだ
Bitch...
ちょ ちょっと待ってくださいね
P-Please wait here!
What's up with her?
どうしたんだ 急に
See you later!
ふふん さては失恋でもした
Are you suffering from a
broken heart or something?
Meat...
肉
あ 図星
Am I right?! Did you really lose a lover?
あんたホントに失恋したの
Dummy!
バカ
You...
おのれ
Stupid! Stupid! Cast-away-woman Yozora! Lame!
バカ バカ 夜空のフられ女
だっさー
んで  誰なのよあんたをフった相手は
So who dumped you?
Whoever it was has good taste for
being able to see that Yozora is poo!
夜空がうんこだって事をちゃんと見抜くなんて
なかなか人を見る目があるじゃない
What the hell are you doing, stupid Yozora?!
ちょっと 何すんのよバカ夜空
私は失恋などしていない
I don't have a broken heart.
だが 私が傷心中の時貴様がどういう反応をするのかはよくわかった
But now I know how you would
react if I ever did suffer from heartache.
What? And here I thought it was
the perfect chance to bully Yozora...
なによ せっかく夜空をいじめるチャンスだと思ったのに
Well, if it's not a broken
heart, why did you cut it?
でも失恋じゃないなら何で切ったの
教えてやらない
I'm not going to tell you!
いいじゃない教えてよ
Oh, come on! Tell me!
Sempai!
先輩 これを着てみてください
Please try this on!
What is that, a boy's uniform
from some other school?
何だ どこかの男子用制服か
That's right, Yozora-sempai!
そうです夜空先輩
これこぞが帝立ガルフォード学院の生徒会長のみ着る事を許される
This is the historic,
legitimate white uniform coat
that only the student council president
由緒正しき白ランなのです
of Galford Academy is allowed to wear!
帝立ガルフォード
Galford... Academy?
Yozora-sempai, I'm sure
it'll look stylish on you!
夜空先輩なら
きっと完璧に着こなせるはずです
こ これはコスプレ衣装というやつではないか
I-Isn't this just a cosplay outfit?
Why should I have to cosplay?
なぜ私がコスプレなどしなければならないのだ
It'll look great on you, trust me! Please!
絶対に似合いますから
お願いします
あ おにちゃん
Big Brother!
おにちゃん  おにちゃん
Big Brother! Big Brother!
今日も元気だな マリアは
You're in high spirits today too, huh, Maria?
Why are you standing in the hall?
何で廊下に立たされているのだ
Did you do something naughty again?
また何か悪い事でもしたのか
What do you mean, "again"?
またってどういう事だ
いいぞ 小鷹
Okay, Kodaka!
What do you think, Kodaka-sempai?!
どうです 小鷹先輩
Um... It looks...
いや その
H-Hot guy! There's a really hot guy in here!
イ イケメンだ  すごいイケメンがおる
Why are you afraid?
何で怖がってるんだ
Hot guys chew up and spit out cute girls!
イケメンはな 可愛い女の子を片っ端から食べてしまうのだ
That's what the other sisters say!
他のシスターが言ってた
And since I'm so cute, I'm sure to be gnawed on!
私はとても可愛いからきっと食べられてしまう
俺様 お前丸かじり
I'm going to munch on you.
おいしくありませんから 私おいしくありませんから
I don't taste good! I don't taste good at all!
I'm going to munch and crunch you.
俺様 お前ボリボリ食べる
- Didn't we go through this before?
- I'm gonna be eaten!
そのやり取り 前にやらなかったか
Bro, my summer homework is...
あんちゃん 夏休みの宿題が
Her! If you're gonna eat
anybody, make it this vampire!
コイツ 食べるならこの吸血鬼がいますから
She tastes better than me!
コイツの方がおいしいですから
You're gonna eat me?
食べると
ああ いや それはその
No, that's just...
Me! Me! Me!
はいはいはい 小鳩ちゃんはあたしが食べる
I'm gonna eat up Kobato-chan!
あたしに
Give her to me...
Hey! What the hell was that for?!
ちょ  何すんのよ
うるさい この変態が
Shut up, pervert! Shame on you! Shame!
恥を知れ 恥を
Yeesh. She comes in after a week's absence,
まったく 久しぶりに顔を出したっていうのに
but even after a haircut, Yozora is Yozora.
やっぱり 髪を切っても所詮夜空は夜空ね
Of course. I am me.
There's no way I would change.
当たり前だ 私は私
変わる訳がなかろう
What should I call you?
お前のこと なんて呼べばいいんだ
Sora?
空
"Yozora." Just like you've
been calling me, "Yozora."
夜空だ これまで通り夜空
Got it, Kodaka?
わかったか 小鷹
Got it, Yozora.
わかった 夜空
Good.
Yozora and I...
俺と夜空は
I mean, Taka and Sora were once good friends.
いや 鷹と空はかつて 確かに友達だった
But now Hasegawa Kodaka
and Mikazuki Yozora aren't.
でも今は 羽瀬川小鷹と三日月夜空はそうじゃない
I know that Yozora was Sora,
夜空が空だと判明したからとかいって
but we can't suddenly go back to
our relationship from ten years ago.
いきなり俺達が10年前の関係に戻る事などできないのだ
Still, what'll happen to us from here on out?
だけど これからの俺達はどうなるんだ
Why did you cut it so short?
どうしてそんなに短かく
私がどういう髪型にしようが
- Can't I have whatever hairstyle I want?
- I don't know that answer right now.
その答えは  今の俺はまだわからない
- As long as you know that it makes
your fox eyes stand out even more.
- I don't know that answer right now.
- What's that, Meat?!
- But that's why I'm
going to stick around here...
だから これからも俺はここにいるのだろう
- Sempai, put on this cape next!
- But that's why I'm
going to stick around here...
QUIVER
WANAWANA グッと Good 弾けてる
Vigorously bursting with goodness
You know, that's surprisingly addicting
Even though you're a dirty vampire...
案外なんだい　ハマってんじゃん
吸血鬼のくせに
Shut up, disciple of God!
Let's get the ball rolling
while you're idly acting shy!
うっさい
人見知りしてる暇に 始めよう！
Here in this club, where the
purpose is to "make friends"...
友達づくりが目的の この部に
Keep falling to the darkness of Hell!
でもでも 絡んじゃって遊んじゃって Yeah!
But-But let's continue to quarrel and play, yeah!
Oh, don't, Student Council President!
I'm not the Student Council President!
I totally, totally want to take a peek
絶対絶対のぞきたい
You! Well? What do you think of that?
You どーだいどーだいそこんとこ
"Neighbors Club"
"We're looking for members!"
We! You know, this is surprisingly addicting
We! 案外なんだいハマってる
All right, let's begin the Neighbors
Club activities for the new term!
では 新学期の隣人部の活動を開始する
Yes! Vigorously bursting with goodness
Yes! グッと Good 弾けてる
FIDGET
SOWASOWA
I don't want to regret this 100 times,
後悔100回したくない
So toss it aside and shake it off
捨てきっちゃって 振りきって
You know, it's surprisingly addicting
Aren't you acting bashful?
案外なんだいハマってる 照れてるんじゃない?
Fight another 100 times, show
your true self and send them flying
もっかい100回ケンカして 見せきっちゃって 蹴飛ばして
Vigorously bursting with goodness
グッと Good 弾けてる
Let's go find some! Let's
make friends and play, yeah!
"Neighbors Club"
"We're looking for members!"
見つけよう! 友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah!
Let's go find some! Let's
make friends and play, yeah!
Aa, nounai souzou risou no genjitsu touhi
あー 脳內 想像理想の 現実逃避
今更どっちだっていっけど 友達作り
Ima sara docchi datte ikkedo... tomodachi zukuri
Hitori sabishii yatsu da to
sagesumu shisen ga ki ni naru
一人寂しい奴だと蔑む 視線が気になる
De, uwattsura dake atsumattara...
で 上っ面だけ集まったら
それでいいと 思っているうちに
Sore de ii to omotte iru uchi ni~
Are yo are yo to toujou, sorotte
あれよあれよと登場 揃って 破天荒な奴らに
Hatenkou na yatsura ni
Maipeesu midasarete yuku
マイペース 乱されてゆく 頭くる！特に憎っくき肉
Atama kuru! Toku ni nikukkuki niku!
Watashi no mune, hisoka
ni asette yuujou fudan kimi de
私の胸秘かに焦って 優柔不斷気味で
My heart tsutaerarenai
My heart 伝えられない 殘念なのは 私なのか
Zannen na no wa watashi na no ka?
Moya moya wo kakiwake Today!
もやもやを かきわけ Today！
Okizari ni sareta otome
gokoro ano hi kara kuyande iru
置き去りにされた 乙女心 あの日から悔やんでいる
Hayaku mitsuke dashite, maigo no kokoro
早く見つけ出して 迷子のココロ
Huh? This is the last
episode... why's there a preview?
You let your guard down too easily, Sempai.
There will actually be an additional episode.
What? What'll it be about?
That's a secret.
Come on, tell me!
Very well, I shall.
Make up your mind!
It's the legendary episode: the tale barred from
broadcast and never before revealed to anyone!
I didn't know we had one of those...
And the title is...
Next time: "A Round-Robin
Story's Ending Is Way Extreme"!
"Next time: A Round-Robin
Story's Ending Is Way Extreme"
I've got a bad feeling about this.
The round-robin story:
the door to a forbidden world!